{
    "id": "fcf44dd7e7f6466390c78f5cf7226df6",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I …………………….. a nice hat for the picnic.",
            "description": "The active verb is used when the subject is the doer of the action.",
            "answers": [
                "bought",
                "was bought",
                "am bought"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The poor dog ……………………….. badly by the cruel master.",
            "description": "Use a passive verb when the subject is the receiver of the action.",
            "answers": [
                "treated",
                "was treated",
                "has treated"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "At school we ………………………… science, mathematics, grammar and history.",
            "description": "Either learned or were taught is here. ",
            "answers": [
                "learned",
                "were learned",
                "were taught"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Who ……………………… the cuckoo to sing so sweetly?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "taught",
                "was taught",
                "were taught"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………… to take a break.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "told",
                "was told"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "All of my questions ………………………….",
            "description": "Use the passive verb form when the subject is not the doer of the action. ",
            "answers": [
                "have answered",
                "have been answered",
                "have been answering"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………….. abroad for higher studies.",
            "description": "The go cannot be used in the passive form.",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "was went",
                "had went"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………….. to a correction home to learn good manners.",
            "description": "Use the passive verb form when the subject is the receiver of the action. ",
            "answers": [
                "sent",
                "was sent",
                "had sent"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………… for twenty years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "imprisoned",
                "was imprisoned",
                "had imprisoned"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The injured man ………………………… to the hospital immediately.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "took",
                "has taken",
                "was taken"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The stolen diamonds …………………………. by the police.",
            "description": "Either have been recovered or were recovered is possible here. Both are in the passive form.",
            "answers": [
                "have recovered",
                "have been recovered",
                "were recovered"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………. of stealing the helmet.",
            "description": "They accused him of stealing the helmet. / He was accused of stealing the helmet. ",
            "answers": [
                "accused",
                "was accused",
                "has accused"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}